{"data":[{"question":"Buses _____ my house every hour.","a":"pass","b":"passes","answer":"1","explain":"- Affirmative: I\/you\/we\/they + V. \n- Buses is plural.","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"1","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"3"},{"question":"He _____ live beside the sea.","a":"don't","b":"doesn't","answer":"2","explain":"- Negative: he\/she\/it + does not\/doesn't + V.","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"1","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"3"},{"question":"_____ Tom enjoy driving at night?","a":"Do","b":"Does","answer":"2","explain":"- Interrogative: Does + he\/she\/it + V...?","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"1","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"3"},{"question":"He _____ too much TV.","a":"watch","b":"watchs","c":"watches","answer":"3","explain":"- Affirmative: he\/she\/it + Vs\/es...\n- Watch -> watches.","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"1","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"2"},{"question":"They _____ their father.","a":"help","b":"helps","c":"helpes","answer":"1","explain":"- Affirmative: I\/you\/we\/they + V.","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"1","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"2"},{"question":"_____ they fly from London to Edinburgh?","a":"Do","b":"Does","answer":"1","explain":"- Interrogative: Do + I\/you\/we\/they + V...?","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"1","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"3"},{"question":"Question7","a":"A ","b":"B","answer":"doesn't","explain":"1","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"1","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"3"},{"question":"Question7","a":"A ","b":"B","answer":"doesn't","explain":"1","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"1","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"3"},{"question":"Their aunt _____ ride a bike.","a":"don't","b":"doesn't","answer":"2","explain":"- Negative: he\/she\/it + does not\/doesn't + V.","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"1","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"3"},{"question":"The last train _____ leave at midnight.","a":"don't","b":"doesn't","answer":"2","explain":"- Negative: he\/she\/it + does not\/doesn't + V.","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"1","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"3"},{"question":"_____ I cash a cheque every month?","a":"Do","b":"Does","answer":"1","explain":"- Interrogative: Do + I\/you\/we\/they + V.","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"1","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"3"}]}